# Witor Sather

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil



satherws@gmail.com



+5562995273858



linkedin.com/in/witorsather

## Summary

My Portfolio: https://witorsather.github.io/

About Me: Data Analyst and Business Intelligence Analyst with 3 years of experience in the telecommunications / HR segments, elaboration of informational and managerial data for decision making. Work in BI teams using agile methodologies, data analysis and modeling, ETL development (extraction, transformation and load). Use of market BI tools such as SSIS (SQL Server Integration Services) and SSAS (SQL Server Analysis Services). Application of best practices, tools and management models to build ETL solutions. Analysis and monitoring of the execution of KPI's deepening.

## **Experience**



## Data Analyst & Business Intelligence

LG lugar de gente

Apr 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

Maintenance of B.I and Analytics projects with Microsoft Power BI and QlikView, using SQL Server database and Azure SaaS. Support in product support. Carry out the approval of new versions, avoiding uploading defective versions in production. Write database queries for data extractions as required by the business. Meet weekly with the planning team, to align the activities to be developed. Analyze and detail errors in the tools whenever necessary, checking where the error occurs and its impact, in order to define priorities for solving the error and forward it to the system development team. Study new technologies through internet research, in order to bring innovations and new solutions that are interesting for the organization. Offer usage guidelines to users in order to train them in the use of the tools. Power BI, QlikView, SQL Server.

## Data Analyst & Business Intelligence - Team Business Intelligence

Tahto

Aug 2020 - Apr 2021 (9 months)

Description: Development of reports and monitoring of their results in order to achieve the desired goals. Studies focusing on operational trends, through the measurement of results and comparisons for decision making. Teradata and SQL Server database. SSIS (SQL Server Integration Services). SAS Enterprise Guide. Excel (Automation of reports with VBA). Power BI.



## **Data Analyst & Business Intelligence - Team Operation**

Tahto

Apr 2019 - Aug 2020 (1 year 5 months)

Preparation of reports, result control and support to the Ombudsman manager. Cell and people management, survey of indicators, deadlines, collection and support to supervisors and areas.

Participation in campaigns, presentation, PDS, creation of new cells and training. Excel (Automation of reports with VBA). Power BI. SQL Server database.

# > Training Developer

Deltta Tecnologia e Soluções Jan 2018 - Feb 2018 (2 months)

### **Education**

Faculdade SENAI Fatesg

Technology Course, Analysis and Systems Development

Aug 2021 - Dec 2023

- Software Engineering;
- · Database Modeling;
- Software Development;
- · Data Structure;

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

SQL Full - Softblue Cursos Online 462591823877

Java First Steps: Programming Logic and Algorithms - Udemy UC-3f0d0b14-0242-4c59-beae-296e133ae2f5

- **Advanced Excel** Faculdade SENAI Fatesg
- Excel VBA Creating Systems + Database Access (SQL) Udemy UC-e98520a2-2320-4eb7-a0a7-9b9dac9a7ac7

#### **Skills**

SQL • Inteligência de negócios (BI) • SSIS • Modelagem de dados • SAS • MySQL • HTML5 • JavaScript • CSS • VBA (Visual Basic for Applications)